Yichi (Lyric) Liu

lyricliu@gatech.edu

+1 (770) 769 - 7254

Portfolio: https://lyricliu.com

(7)

https://dribbble.com/YICHILIU



https://vimeo.com/lyricliu



Personal Statement

I specialize in web design & development, illustration, video & animation.

My design approach roots in strategic thinking that extends to visual designs crafted with intent. I strive to make all my projects beautiful and elegant. Armed with the latest technologies I have a head full of ideas.

*

My Specialties

01. Computer		02. Knowledge
Adobe Photoshop Adobe Illustratior	• • • • • • • • •	Grid & Layout
CorelDRAW		Typograph
HTML / CSS JavaScript / Jquery	• • • • • • • • •	Color theory Animation theory
D3.js / node.js	• • • • • • • •	Prototyping
Adobe After Effects Adobe Premiere	• • • • • • • • •	Image editing Web usability
Cinema 4D Autodesk Maya	• • • • • • • • •	Interface Design
Unity 3D	• • • • • • • • •	



Experience

Oct. 2015 - July. 2016

Cowoof Application Development

Participated in a social networking application development as a freelancer. Cowoof is a California company for dog lovers.

Jun. 2015 - Aug. 2015

HiMedia Company (Shenzhen) UI design Internship Designed web UI for side projects. Planned an online marketing activity which engaged more than ten thousands participants.

Oct. 2012 - July. 2014

Non-profit Organization Enactus Involvement

Participated in a female assistant project supported by Walmart. Received Elite Student 2013 Award from Enactus - China.

Education

Aug. 2016 - May. 2018

Georgia Institute of Technology

MS. in Digital Media GPA: 4.0 / 4.0

Sep. 2012 - Jun. 2016

Huazhong University of Sci. & Tech.

BA. in Communication BE. in Computer Science

Major **GPA: 3.91 / 4.0**, Rank: **No.1** / 30

Jan. 2015 - May. 2015

University of California Berkeley

Visiting Student in Sociology

Recognitions

10%

Jun. 2016

Outstanding Graduate
Huazhong U. of Sci. & Tech.

%

Sep. 2014

National Scholarship Ministry of Education of China

st

Nov. 2014

Grand Prize Winner Wuhan HTML5 Game Design Contest

Language Skills

ChineseMother Language

English Advanced Level

German Basic Level



My hobbies









